<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Docent</string>
    <string-array name="targetMrlArray">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answerArray">
        <item>Choose answer</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Not Applicable</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="threadsArray">
        <item>Technology Maturity</item>
        <item>Industrial Base</item>
        <item>Manufacturing Technology Development</item>
        <item>Producibility Program</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteriaThread0">
        <item>Thread</item>
        <item>Sub-Thread</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteriaThread1">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 1</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 2</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 3</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 4</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 5</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 6</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 7</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 7 or TRL 8</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 8 or TRL 9</item>
        <item>Should be assessed at TRL 9</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteriaThread2">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Potential sources identified to address technology needs. Understand state of the art.</item>
        <item>Industrial base capabilities surveyed and known gaps/risks identified for preferred concept, key technologies, components, and/or key processes.</item>
        <item>Industrial base capabilities assessment initiated to identify potential manufacturing sources. Sole/single/ foreign source vendors and vendors of technologies with potential obsolescence issues have been identified and planning has begun to minimize risks.</item>
        <item>Industrial base capabilities assessment for MS B has been completed. Industrial capability in place to support manufacturing of development articles. Plans to minimize sole/foreign sources and obsolescence issues complete. Need for sole/single/foreign sources justified. Potential alternative sources identified.</item>
        <item>Industrial capability to support production has been analyzed. Sole/single/foreign sources stability and obsolescence issues are assessed/monitored. Developing potential alternate sources as necessary.</item>
        <item>Industrial base capability assessment for MS C has been completed. Industrial capability is in place to support LRIP. Sources are available, multi-sourcing where cost-effective or necessary to mitigate risk.</item>
        <item>Industrial capability assessment for FRP has been completed and capability is in place to support start of FRP.</item>
        <item>Industrial capability supports FRP. Industrial capability assessed to support modifications, upgrades, surge and other potential manufacturing requirements.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteriaThread3">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>New manufacturing concepts and potential solutions identified.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing technology concepts identified through experiments/models.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing Science and Advanced Manufacturing Technology requirements identified.</item>
        <item>Required manufacturing technology development efforts initiated, if applicable.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing technology efforts continuing. Required manufacturing technology development solutions demonstrated in a production relevant environment.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing technology efforts continuing. Required manufacturing technology development solutions demonstr ated in a production representative environment.</item>
        <item>Primary manufacturing technology efforts concluding and some improvement efforts continuing. Required manufacturing technology solutions validated on a pilot line.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing technology process improvement efforts initiated for FRP.</item>
        <item>Manufacturing technology continuous process improvements ongoing.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="criteriaThread4">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item>Relevant materials/processes evaluated for manufacturability using experiments/models.</item>
        <item>Initial producibility and manufacturability assessment of preferred systems concepts completed. Results considered in selection of preferred design concepts and reflected in AS key components/technologies.</item>
        <item>Producibility and manufacturability assessments of key technologies and components initiated as appropriate. Ongoing design trades consider manufacturing processes and industrial base capability constraints. Manufacturing processes assessed for capability to test and verify in production, and influence on operations and support.</item>
        <item>Producibility assessments and producibility trade studies (performance vs. producibility) of key technologies/components completed. Results used to shape Acquisition Strategy, SEP, Manufacturing and Producibility plans, and planning for EMD or technology insertion programs. Preliminary design choices assessed against manufacturing processes and industrial base capability constraints. Producibility enhancement efforts (e.g., Design for Manufacturing and Design for Assembly</item>
        <item>Detailed producibility trade studies using knowledge of key design characteristics and related manufacturing process capability completed. Producibility enhancement efforts (e.g., Design for Manufacturing, Design for Assembly)ongoing for optimized integrated system. Manufacturing processes reassessed as needed for capability to test and verify potential influence on operations and support.</item>
        <item>Producibility improvements implemented on system. Known producibility issues have been resolved and pose no significant risk for LRIP.</item>
        <item>Prior producibility improvements analyzed for effectiveness during LRIP. Producibility issues/risks discovered in LRIP have been mitigated and pose no significant risk for FRP.</item>
        <item>Design producibility improvements demonstrated in FRP. Process producibility improvements ongoing. All modifications, upgrades, DMSMS, and other changes assessed for producibility.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="deskbookVersions">
        <item>V2.4 - August 2015</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_questionnaire">QuestionnaireActivity</string>
</resources>
